

hilal@sharifli.com

BAKU, Azerbaijan

+994552068674

Profile

Experienced IT System Administrator mainly experienced in telecom-based technologies bringing forth the ability to effectively operate and provide support for various systems. Adept in setting up and integrating systems with required configurations, and experienced in managing the functionality of systems. Resourceful, and committed to continually advancing my knowledge of relevant technologies.

Employment History

Social Survey Specialist, Synergetics LLC, BAKU

October 2005 — July 2006

As a student started working in this company part-time. Worked as an operator. Collected social survey information in software called SPSS.

Specialist of CAD software, Sulaco LLC, BAKU

July 2006 - July 2007

As student started working in this company part time. Worked as a specialist in software called AutoCad, in wich prepared various schemes for companies project. Left this jobto perform military service.

ERP Projects Technical Analyst, CTR Group, BAKU

November 2008 — June 2011

The company was providing various IT solutions for it is customers, mainly concentrated in ERP related projects.

I have been involved in providing it support in implementation of ERP software. Worked inmultiple projects.

Project Coordination Specialist, AZERFON, BAKU

June 2011 — October 2012

Worked as project coordination specialist in Information Technology Department. Coordinated various projects related with IT and Telecom. Earned valuable experience in GSM technologies.

Head of IT Support and Maintenance team, VOIDA LLC, BAKU

March 2013

Planned and prepared various IT infrastructures for the company's projects. Have been working the project related to telecommunications companies and Banks. Provided supporting the process of Implementation of new technologies. Prepared the company's Server and Network equipment. Have experience with integration and support of IN projects.

Integrated multiple IVR systems in SIP and SS7 protocols.

Prepared and implemented UAT cases and plans. Communicated frequently with clients regarding application functionality requirements.

Education

Bachelor, Baku State University, BAKU September 2003 — June 2007 Faculty of Geography, Hidrology

September 2008 — June 2010	
MBA (Computer Information Systems)	
Links	
<u>Linkedin Profile</u> <u>Personal Website</u>	
Skills	
Networking	SS7
ISUP	Computer Networking
Linux Administration	Project Management
Vmware ESXI	Voip
Asterisk PBX	Zabbix
Docker	Bash Scripting
Ansible	Veeam Backup and Replication
Apache Tomcat	Nginx
Mysql	Microsoft Sql Server
Oracle	Smpp
Languages	
Russian	Azerbaijani
English	

Master, Azerbaijan State University of Oil and Industry, BAKU

Hobbies

Diving, Hunting, Fishing